

Mimi Ojserkis

Full Stack Software Engineer

About Me

Full Stack Software Engineer excited to find her place in the tech world! Experienced in JavaScript, React, Ruby on Rails, Ruby, and SQL with a background in tech sales. Posses strong skills in leadership that help tech companies drive results in teamoriented environments.

mimioj@gmail.com 609-457-7718 New York, NY 10023 linkedin.com/in/mimio github.com/Mimioj101 medium.com/@mimioj

Education

Software Engineering Flatiron School

JULY 2020 - OCT 2020

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

Bachelors of Arts in Psychology & Communications Rutgers University

SEPT 2012 - MAY 2016

Cum Laude Psi Chi Honor Society Lambda Pi Eta Honor Society

Technical Skills & Proficiencies

Ruby ReactJS Ruby Geocoder

JavaScript Ruby on Rails HTTParty

CSS AWS HTML

SQL JQuery API's

Technical Projects

WikiLeeks

A WikiPedia search & save web application.

GITHUB || DEMO

Trail Mixer

A social hiking companion with the ability to discover trails across the country.

GITHUB || DEMO

G.Wiz

An SAT prep & Word association quiz app.

GITHUB || DEMO

- Communicated RESTfully between React frontend and Rails backend.
- Utilized JSON Web Tokens and localStorage to store encrypted user information client-side.
- Customized API calls to MediaWiki's API through a self-built proxy to give search functionality.
- Tailored API calls to TheHikerProject's API to give search functionality.
- Implemented Ruby Geocoder gem to geocode a search location into longitude and latitude.
- Interacted RESTfully between vanilla JavaScript frontend and Rails backend.
- Customized API calls using HTTParty via Rails backend.

Professional Experience

Account Executive, Sales Innovation

Glassdoor

DEC 2019 - MAY 2020

- Pioneered Self-Serve Sales pilot product.
- Communicated with product engineers and other Go-To-Market sales teams to improve product and sales process.

Account Executive

The Sliding Door Company

JAN 2019 - DEC 2019

- Operated in a fast-paced environment, through a high daily volume of activity including outbound calls, emails, webbased presentations, and social selling.
- Builded trust with clients and maintained a wealth of productbased knowledge.